All right,
we're good to go.
You got this?
You bet your ass, bubba.
Let's make some money!
Everyone in position.
l thought we'd be
robbing banks by now,
not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.
Down here,
gas is gold,
bubba.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(LAUGHS)
(RADlO SQUEALS)
DOM ON RADIO :
Kill the chatter!
Game time.
l wouldn't
piss him off,
guys.
(lGUANA GROWLS)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
DOM : Okay, guys,
we're gonna have to hit
this hard and fast.
We got four K left
before the downgrade.
(TlRES SQUEAL)
Locked and loaded !
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(TRUCK HONKlNG)
(SPRAYlNG)
(TRUCK CONTlNUES HONKlNG)
(GRUNTS)
This is all you, Han.
Liquid gold.
(CHUCKLES)
We're clear.
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can
get it under six tries
this time, huh, T?
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
lt's more like three.
Come on, Tego,
keep it real.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Just one K left. We're running out of road.
Get in there, brother.
l got it, l got it.
(YELLS)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Shit!
(GRUNTS)
T, cut loose!
Unhitch, unhitch !
(SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(BOTH SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(ENGlNE REVVlNG)
Spray that hitch !
l don't have a hammer!
Just do it!
(SCREAMS)
Hold on ! Hold on !
No shit!
Hold onto
something tight!
(METAL CLANKS)
DOM : Letty!
Give me your hand !
l can't reach !
You got to jump!
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Jump!
Letty, jump!
l've got you !
(GROANS)
Dom. . .
Dom?
Dom !
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
(CARS REVVlNG)
(EXCLAlMS)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
HAN : How you doing?
OMAR : Money, money!
Good.
OMAR : Yo, why your stack
is bigger than mine always?
TEGO : l'm supersized,
baby.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Cops just raided
our garage in Baracoa.
They were real
interested in you.
Heat's on and we just
sent up a flare that's gonna
lead them right to us.
l say we move out
first thing
in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me,
they're throwing big numbers
at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go
do your own thing.
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
(SlGHS)
l hear Rio is nice
this time of year.
The cops are
getting hungrier.
Then l guess
we're doing our job.
l'm a walking target.
l don't want you
around when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die,"
remember?
Dom, how long
have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden,
out of nowhere,it's too dangerous?
Come on.
We'll figure it out.
We always do.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(MAN PANTlNG)
(CAR HONKlNG)
(GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PEOPLE EXCLAlMlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
(PEOPLE SHOUTlNG)
(GUNSHOTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
(BABY CRYlNG)
(WOMAN SCREAMlNG)
(PANTlNG)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROANlNG)
l don't know shit!
Give me a name!
l don't know shit, man !
David Park!
David Park's the guy you want!
Please!
Thank God. Listen,
he's in a mood because yesterday was his cheat day,
and then today,
some genius brought in donuts.
Great.
BRIAN : Sorry l'm late.
(SCOFFS)
Complaints keep rolling in
after your little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating you
wasn't a mistake.
l got a name.
David Park. That's it?
That's all you got?
David Park?
l could throw a fortune cookie
out this window and hit 50 David Parks right now.
lt's Korean,
not Chinese. Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits
street racers to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find Park,
and we bust the bad guys.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(BOY SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
MIA : Dom.
Mia, l told you
not to call me here.
Dom, it's Letty.
She's been murdered.
PRIEST : We have gathered here to pay
our final respects to. . .
Let us reflect
on her journey. . .
"The Lord is my shepherd,
l shall not want. He makes me lie down. . ."
(SOBBlNG)
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto
about 1 0 minutes after
he crossed the border.
l don't get it.
l thought he'd show.
l told you not to come.
They're staking the place out.
lf they find you. . .
They won't.
Come on.
Look at you.
Letty wouldn't
let them junk it.
Even though it is
a goddamn curse.
When she came back,
she was always in here,
working on it day and night.
lt was weird.
lt was like she knew
you were coming back.
l want to see the crash site.
PENNING : l just got off the phone with Deputy Director Lawson.
lf we don't make serious inroads into the Braga case in the next 72 hours,
they're gonna shut us down.
l know l'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?
Because it's been two years,
and the last three agents
we sent to infiltrate his organization
came back in body bags.
He's moved more heroin across the border
than Escobar did in 1 0 years.
This guy is becoming one of our biggest
national threats,
and we don't even
have a picture of him.
We don't have prints!
Not even a goddamn DOB!
What's the status
on David Park?
lsn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?
We're running the name through
city and county databases, sorting the possibilities.
We've got
over 500 already.
Park's insignificant.
Sounds like another jerk-off to me.
BRIAN : lt's not. Without Park,
Braga wouldn't have drivers to move his shipments.
Cross-check traffic.
lllegal modifications.
Street racing. This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.
We better.
(CHUCKLES)
What do you know?
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has been spotted
in his old neighborhood.
l'm going to
bring his ass in.
Not in your car
you're not.
lt's straight ahead.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)
(GROANlNG)
(GUN COCKlNG)
(GUNSHOT)
You found something
back there.
There were burn marks
on the ground.
The kind that could
only be caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in all of L.A.
that sells that.
Nothing you can do is gonna bring
her back, Dom.
lf l were Letty,
l would ask you. . .
No, l would beg you,
please, let this go.
Before it's too late.
lt's already too late.
l love you.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR DOOR OPENlNG)
STASIAK :
Miss Toretto.
l'm Michael Stasiak, FBl.
Let's you and l
have a little chat.
(ELEVATOR BELL DlNGS)
Hi. This is Forsythe
in Evidence.
l need Stasiak down here right away
to sign some greenies.
Thanks.
Hi.
Hey.
Okay, l narrowed it down
to 50 or so David Parks.
What l'd like you to do is run the make and model on each one of them.
All right?
Okay. All right.
Thank you.
(DOOR BUZZES)
Hey, Tyler,
we got a transfer.
You want to
come with me?
(ROCK MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Toretto.
When'd you get
back in town?
l'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford full-size.
Continental tires.
Look, what are you doing,
coming in here like this, huh?
This ain't your scene
anymore, boss.
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, okay?
Say hi to your
sister for me.
(GRUNTlNG)
(GROANlNG)
A Korean kid brought it in.
David Park.
lt's a green Ford Torino.
Please don't
drop this on me!
l'm almost done.
Why don't you tell me
why you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going
to capture Dom. Maybe worse.
l don't want you getting tangled up in this.
So stay away from him.
That's what you have to say to me
after five years?
All of a sudden, you care
what happens to me.
What l did to you
was wrong.
l'm sorry. lt was. . .
lt was the hardest thing l've ever had to do.
l'm sorry, too, Brian.
l'm so sorry that you had
to come into my home and pretend to love me.
l'm so sorry that you ripped
my family apart.
l'm very sorry that that was
hard for you.
l lied to you.
l lied to Dom.
l lied to everybody.
That's what l do best.
lt's why the Feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying
to yourself.
Maybe you're not the good guy
pretending to be a bad guy.
Maybe you're the bad guy
pretending to be the good guy.
You ever think about that?
Every day.
l always wondered,
why did you let
my brother go that day?
l don't know.
Shit.
Brian !
l got the cross-checks on David Park back and
have a list of possibles.
What do you got? All right. A 45-year-old
male in a '06 Scion
with three reckless
driving tickets.
No.
An '01 Chevy Tahoe.
Two Mini Coopers,
a '06 and a '07,
a Toyota hybrid.
Hell no.
A '98 Saturn,
a '95 Sebring.
A '98 Nissan 240
with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
What?
The 240 with
the illegal mod.
How do you know?
'Cause that's something
l'd drive.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Green Torino,
running nitro.
Whose car?
l don't know, man.
l'm just the middleman.
l swear!
l'm just the middleman !
(GROANS)
(PANTlNG)
Wait, wait, wait.
l don't know shit, man.
l swear. l just run
cars for Braga, all right?
All l can do is
get you in the race!
That's all l can do!
What race?
(SCREAMlNG)
Help! Come on,
hold on !
Let me up, man !
Come on !
Come on, man,
l don't know shit!
Just let me up!
l told you,
you got to
talk to Braga!
Bring him up, Dom.
God ! Don't drop me!
That's all l know!
Bring him up.
You here to take
me in, O'Conner?
Shit! Shit!
Shut up!
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't
anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys
talk about this later?
Now pull my ass up!
She was running
for this guy, Braga,
and things went bad.
Please!
l'm going to
get these guys, Dom.
Now let me do my job
and bring him up.
l'm going to
kill this Braga.
God !
And anyone else
who gets in my way.
Hey!
Don't let go.
O'Conner!
O'Conner! lf you ever release
a witness of mine again. . .
(GROANS)
That's enough !
STASIAK :
Don't touch me.
l'm fine!
PENNING : That's enough.
You're through, O'Conner!
l said that's enough !
Stasiak, go get
yourself cleaned up.
What?
He hit me first! You. . .
This isn't
the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on !
You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference between
a cop and a criminal?
What?
One bad judgment call.
Keep your shit in line,
son.
Have a good time.
Take a seat.
Good news. We have intel that Braga's
number two, Ramon Campos,
will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night
to fill a slot
on his team.
They've already chosen three drivers
from previous races.
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park,
has been kind enough
to get us into the race.
O'Conner, you're up.
Let me guess,
winner gets the slot.
(CHUCKLES)
All right, so these are
all the imports the city has in impound.
Okay, nice.
Pick your poison.
All right, 2206.
l crashed one of those.
341 8 and 2765.
Okay, so which one
do you want?
l want them all.
Standard issue
tracking device.
Boss wants to know
where you are at all times.
(WHlRRlNG)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
(CAMPOS SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
You want to
play with it?
DWIGHT : Hey!
(SNlCKERS)
What are you
looking at, nutsack?
l don't know.
You tell me.
The racer wants
what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies,
Dwight's already on the team.
You got to be fast
if you want to drive for Braga.
ls there
a problem here?
No.
You one of
Park's guys, blondie?
Yeah. Yeah, l am.
Follow me.
(SOFTLY)
See you later, punk.
You, too, punk.
FENIX : Bull's-eye, coño,
come on !
(CAMPOS EXCLAlMS)
FENIX : We can do this all day.
(CAMPOS SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
You all know
why you're here.
Good drivers
are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's
got a chingadera tuner
racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that
would sell their abuelita
to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives
their 1 0-second cars
not in a straight line,
but to push it and
make it through places
no one else would take it.
Real drivers.
So, what are we hauling?
CAMPOS : For the money
Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.
You just said
you wanted
real drivers.
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Mira, real driver,
nobody's forcing you
to race.
You the boss?
Or am l talking
to the boss?
Do l look like a boss?
My job is to find
the best drivers,
period.
Whoever wins the race
gets the info. We cool?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
RACER: No,
we ain't cool, man.
Who's closing these streets?
(CHUCKLlNG)
No one.
That's the point.
(CAR ENGlNES REVVlNG)
AUTOMATED VOICE ON GPS :
PIease wait whiIe
directions are downIoaded.
Proceed to
the highlighted route.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six...
You sure
you want to do this?
A lot has changed.
...four...
You're right.
...three,
two,
one,
go!
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
Right turn ahead.
You are now five miIes
from your destination.
(HONKlNG)
How's my ass look,
Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
(CARS HONKlNG)
(TRUCK HONKS)
Dead man driving.
Come on !
Right turn ahead.
(SCREAMS)
Shit!
Damn.
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead.
(HONKlNG)
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
Shit.
Rerouting.
Just shut up!
You are 2.6 miIes
from destination.
Oops, l didn't see you.
You are now four
and one-haIf miIes
from your destination.
(CAR HONKlNG)
U-turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 miIes
from your destination.
Sorry, car.
You are now one miIe
from your destination.
Yeah,
guess who's back, Dom?
Let's go!
Nice car, baby!
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
(SlGHS lN RELlEF)
Bitch !
You are now
one-quarter mile
from your destination.
(ENGlNE REVVlNG)
Too early, Dom.
(TlRES SQUEAL)
No!
Still a buster.
(PEOPLE CHEERlNG)
You have reached
your destination.
Goodbye.
At least we know
you can't beat me
straight up.
l didn't know
there were any rules.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Now that's what l call
real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man !
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now.
When the GPS calls,
you follow.
Driver's license.
What driver's license?
Thumb.
Cell phone number.
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me.
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you
something, man, muscle
beats import every time.
You know what
l'm saying?
Every time!
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.
DWIGHT : Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.
So beautiful.
(CHUCKLES)
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
Yes, baby!
Daddy Dwight loves. . .
BRIAN : FBl !
l didn't do nothing, man !
Dwight didn't do nothing !
Hey, no! Stay, stay!
Where you going?
WOMAN : Bye, Dwight!
No, what did l do?
(EXCLAlMS lN PAlN)
BRIAN : You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not
supposed to.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
Live it up!
(HlP-HOP MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad
about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
l wish l could say
l was surprised to see you here.
What's to stop someone
from telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me from telling them why you're really here.
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?
Great. You having a good time?
Yeah, a great time.
Come on,
let's have a better time.
How's your car?
lt took a nasty bump.
BRIAN : lt'll be ready.
l also heard you just
got out of County.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
You know a guy
named Jim Garcia?
Nah. Big place.
Lots of names, lots of faces.
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.
Yeah, that kind of heat
can't be good for business.
Yeah, well, that depends
on how you look at things.
l go down, l do time.
l do real time.
l don't know about your other drivers, but when l see flashing lights in my mirror,
l don't stop.
Do you know each other?
He used to date
my sister.
l see.
You're a lucky man.
How's that?
You're still breathing.
(CHUCKLES)
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.
(CAMPOS TOASTlNG lN SPANlSH)
So, what's Braga about?
You know,
he's just one of us.
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.
Now he's a shot caller.
The boss of bosses.
See all these
cats in here?
Any one of them
would die for Braga.
lncluding you?
Especially me.
(WHlSPERlNG)
Enjoy the party, fellows.
Club's yours.
Whatever you want,
booze, broads, it's all good.
Braga's mine.
l'm taking the
whole house down.
Good luck.
(CLUB MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(ELEVATOR BELL RlNGS)
(MEN CHATTERlNG)
Something interests you
about this car?
Just admiring
the body work.
Are you one of those boys
who prefers cars to women?
l'm one of those boys that appreciates a fine body,
regardless of the make.
Your car?
lt's Fenix's car.
You'll meet him at the rendezvous.
He'll be leading you.
So now
that l know
your taste in cars,
tell me,
what about
your women?
lt all starts
with the eyes.
She's got to have those kind of eyes that can look
right through the bullshit
to the good in someone.
20% angel,
80% devil.
Down to earth.
Ain't afraid to get a little engine grease
under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound
anything like me.
lt ain't.
Hi.
l got a gift for you.
All right.
A dirty shot glass,
just what l always wanted.
l got these
from the club last night.
There's two sets
of prints here. Run them both.
l know one of these is Campos'. l think
the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have
to go beyond lnterpol.
So, that means l have to contact
individual agencies,
and that could
take weeks. Okay.
(GPS VlBRATlNG)
(CARS HONKlNG)
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah.
That's your third traffic violation in
less than three blocks.
Slow it down,
O'Conner.
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped.
(BUG DETECTOR BUZZlNG)
(BEEPlNG)
We lost him.
He killed the tracker.
We don't know that.
l'm telling you,
he killed the tracker. We don't know that yet!
Get the bird overhead.
PILOT ON RADIO : Right now,
I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear.
PILOT ON RADIO :
Base, fIag nine, I'm at AngeIs 5.
I don't have a taIIy on the target. Repeat, I don't have a taIIy on the target.
They're gone,
there's no one down there.
Damn it!
TASH : This ain't right, bro. Nobody said nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it.
Hey. Hey!
Yo!
Where do you think they're taking us?
Don't matter.
We're all just along
for the ride now.
Welcome to Mexico, boys.
There are helicopters
and surveillance cameras
that scan for heat
signatures at the border.
But there are blind spots that l can guide you
through via satellite.
There can be no margin of error, so you must
follow my every direction.
Any questions?
l thought Fenix
was gonna be here.
He'll meet you
out there.
All right,
everybody, sync up.
Good luck, gentlemen.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
GISELE ON RADIO :
SateIIite Iinkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.
Stay cIose to Fenix.
He'II Iead you across.
(BEEPlNG)
(MONlTOR BEEPlNG)
l got a heat signature northbound
along Legardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
MAN : Manual override. Rerouting camera to designated coordinates.
GISELE : Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.
(CAR ENGlNES REVVlNG)
Shit.
Toretto,
get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
l don't see anything.
They're gone.
Get the helicopters
to cover it.
PILOT ON RADIO : Base,
we're 40 seconds out from Legardo Ravine.
GISELE : They're sending
a heIicopter.
You have 30 seconds.
PILOT : North 32' 33',
west 1 1 6' 49'.
GISELE : The window
is cIosing fast.
You need to get out of there before
they send ground support.
Fifteen seconds.
PILOT : Base,
target is at two miIes.
GISELE : You're running
out of time.
You need to get out now!
PILOT : Base,
we're at north 32' 33', west 1 1 6' 49'.
We have no visuaI contact.
RoII ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing, man?
(GAS HlSSlNG)
Come on.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Get out.
Come on, man.
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.
MALIK : Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man !
(MAN SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Hey,
l said don't touch me, man !
Hey, look, dawg,
don't put your hands on me.
TASH : Hey,
Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?
(GUN COCKS)
DOM : Hey, boss man !
What did you say?
l said only pussies
run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
l'm talking to you.
Got something on your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty.
Yo.
Where's my money?
DOM : And somebody
wrecked her car.
l wrecked her car.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
You remember her face?
Huh?
'Cause l don't.
Last time l saw it,
it was burning.
Now what?
l'm going to enjoy
what happens next.
(MAN SCREAMlNG)
(GUNFlRE)
(GRUNTlNG)
(GUNSHOT)
(MAN GROANS)
Dom, get in !
Get in ! Come on !
(ALARM BLARlNG)
Come on ! Get in the fucking car!
Let's go! Hurry up!
(HELlCOPTERS WHlRRlNG
lN DlSTANCE)
(PHONE DlALlNG)
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
PENNING : What
have you got, Trinh?
We're contacting agencies
in multiple countries.
Unfortunately, most of them have to manually scan their prints for us to upload.
O'Conner's on line five.
And, sir,
you should see this.
Thank you.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Talk to me, O'Conner.
Where the heII have you been?
l got the shipment.
"l got the shipment,"
or "we got the shipment"?
What are you
taIking about?
Traffic cams in the area
picked up pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me, O'Conner.
Bring in the shipment and bring in Toretto.
But l thought the point was to get Braga.
We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock
stopped ticking.
Bring them in.
Are we cIear?
O'Conner?
(PHONE BEEPS)
So this is what
$60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to
get you to a doctor.
We got to find
a place to hide this.
l got a spot.
502, wet reckless.
l need a 48-hour hold.
Out back.
Any spot you can find.
You sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check, their own impound yard. Trust me.
You know,
l've been thinking,
when you blew up your car back there,
you blew up mine, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So now you owe me
a 1 0-second car.
ls that right?
Yeah.
Now we're even.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
ls this your way of keeping me
away from him?
You're the only one
l could call.
He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
l'm gonna clean it and stitch it up.
lt's going to hurt.
l bet you're going
to enjoy this.
A little.
MIA : Want some of this?
DOM : Yeah.
MIA : lt's spicy.
l like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first,
you have to say grace.
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing this table.
With food, family
and friendship.
You asked me
why l let Dom go.
l think it's because
at that moment,
l respected him
more than l did myself.
Yeah.
One thing l learned from Dom is that nothing really matters unless you have a code.
And what's your code,
Brian?
l'm working on it.
(BEEPS)
(PHONE DlALlNG)
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Shit. Hey, Dom.
When were you gonna tell me?
Dom, what are you doing?
When were you gonna tell me
you were running Letty?
Let me explain. . .
When were you gonna. . .
Dom, stop!
You don't understand.
l don't understand?
Stop!
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
She did it for. . .
(GROANlNG)
BRIAN : Dom, stop!
Dom, stop it!
Please stop!
(BRlAN GRUNTlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
She did it for you, Dom !
She did it for you !
Letty came to me to clear your name in exchange
for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you
to come home!
(YELLS)
l'm sorry, Dom !
l'm sorry!
(SlGHlNG) You better have one hell of an explanation. You disobeyed a direct order.
Where's the shipment?
lt's safe.
Look, we could use the shipment to parade
in front of the media,
get a few hundred pounds of heroin
off the street,
but Braga's just gonna send another shipment next week and the week after that.
Let's use the shipment
to lure Braga out
and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you
suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand
exchange with Braga.
He'll never show.
He can't afford not to.
You got a plan?
There's a price.
We bag Braga,
you let Toretto walk.
(RlNGlNG)
Yes?
It's Dom.
I was just
thinking about you.
You know, when l gave you my number,
l was hoping you'd call.
But not under
these circumstances.
What circumstances?
Me being alive?
Don't take it personaIIy.
lt's just business.
I got some business
of my own.
Get Campos.
lt's them.
Uh-huh.
Was that how Braga inspires loyalty?
Killing his drivers?
One can always
find more drivers.
It's just good business.
l want to trade.
Braga doesn't negotiate.
(SCOFFS) Fine.
You explain to him how all of a sudden $60 million worth of product disappears.
l know that can't
be good for business.
What do you want?
Six million cash,
delivered by Braga himself.
(LAUGHlNG)
I don't Iike being shot at.
l ain't gonna put my neck out again unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it.
Either l deal with Braga,
or you do.
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite.
Holding positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscIe untiI
O'Conner gives the signaI.
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy,
you walk out of here
a free man.
ls that what
they told you?
Yeah, that's the deal.
You still put milk
and cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah.
Here.
ln case things go shitty.
Just like old times?
Yeah.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
You dropped something.
That's what
you wanted, right?
Dom. . .
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(BOTH SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
He's harmless.
Don't worry about him.
And he's really
sorry about Letty.
Where's our stuff?
You mean the stuff
that used to be
in here, right?
Well, you'll see it
when we see Braga. That was the deal.
No worries.
Braga keeps his word.
(BEEPlNG)
$2 million.
You get the rest
when l get my property.
Stasiak.
TRINH: We got a match.
The fingerprint's
Braga's 1 00%.
Just waiting on
faciaI confirmation via fax.
BRIAN : I got
a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were clawing
your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents
to move in.
We got confirmation.
Primary suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move.
Sir, O'Conner hasn't
given us the signal yet.
What part of that didn't you understand?
We just got confirmation. Do it!
FBI AGENT :
Secure primary suspect in gray suit. Repeat!
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit.
You're thinking
what l'm thinking, right?
He ain't Braga.
Oh, shit.
SWAT AGENT 1 :
Drop your weapons!
SWAT AGENT 2 : FBl !
Get down !
(GUNFlRE)
Get out of here!
Get out of here, Dom !
(CAR ENGlNE REVVlNG)
Run him down.
Go!
Campos is Braga!
(MEN GROANlNG)
Come on.
(PEOPLE SHOUTlNG)
SWAT LEADER :
Approaching primary target.
SWAT AGENT ON RADIO :
Primary suspect is secure.
INVESTIGATOR :
He was under your nose the whoIe time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south,
probably long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea
the kind of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
l was doing my job.
He ain't the first bad guy
you helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now,
you're being taken off active duty,
until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.
What about Braga?
That's no longer
your concern.
We now know where Braga is,
right?
Customs tracked him via satellite to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
Mexico is out
of our jurisdiction.
The fact is
the brass will be so busy
holding press conferences over the seizure,
we'll skate
under the radar.
l thought we signed on
to do the right thing.
Everyone's looking for you.
l'm right here.
lt's nice to see
you've gone with the times
and switched to electronic fuel injection.
Looks good.
Buster became a gearhead.
l'm going with you.
l don't plan on
bringing anyone back.
l know.
Hit that throttle.
(SlGHlNG)
Hey.
(BOTTLES CLATTERlNG)
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?
You don't.
(ENGlNE REVVlNG)
l thought you weren't
gonna show up.
You saved my life.
l'm willing to
return the favor.
This will help
get you to Braga.
Dom.
Going in there
is suicide.
l have no choice.
You must have
loved her very much.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
So this is where
my jurisdiction ends.
And this is where
mine begins.
(ALL SHOUTlNG)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(DOOR OPENlNG)
(DOOR CLOSlNG)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(BOTH SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(REClTlNG PRAYER)
You ain't forgiven.
You boys want
to arrest me?
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy
your way out of this one.
You and me. . .
You and me,
we're not so different.
You're no hero.
You're right.
And that's why you're going back
across the border.
(HANDCUFFS CLlCKlNG)
But Fenix is mine.
You got it.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
(DOOR CLOSlNG)
Shit!
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
You'll make it
a couple of miles out,
if you're lucky.
(CARS HONKlNG)
(PEOPLE SHOUTlNG)
(MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH
ON RADIO)
(ALL SHOUTlNG)
(PEOPLE CHEERlNG)
(EXCLAlMS)
(WHlSPERlNG)
(CHUCKLES)
You know where
you're going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
(LAUGHlNG)
Where are your boys at?
Are they going
to show up or what?
(GUNFlRE)
Careful what you ask for.
Just stop.
Just stop the car.
(SCREAMlNG)
(SHOUTlNG lN SPANlSH)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Right behind you.
Dom, head to the tunnel.
Let's use the tunnel.
(GUNSHOT)
Get out of here, Brian.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
You sure you know
where the tunnels are? You sure?
Yeah. l'd hold on.
This might hurt.
You're in
my world now, baby!
(YELLS)
(BANGlNG)
That's it, baby!
End of the road.
Now what?
Game over.
No, no, no.
(YELLS)
(GUNFlRE)
(MAN SCREAMS)
Come on !
(LAUGHlNG)
(GROANS)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(PlLLAR CRACKlNG)
(YELLS)
(BANGlNG)
(GRUNTS)
CAMPOS : Hey!
Get me out of here!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTlNG)
(SlGHS)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(GRUNTS)
(COCKS GUN)
Pussy.
(GROANlNG)
Let me see that.
Yeah.
Just keep pressure there.
(POLlCE SlRENS WAlLlNG)
You'll be all right.
(HELlCOPTERS WHlRRlNG)
You gotta get
out of here.
l ain't running anymore.
l gotta ask you
something.
Yeah?
You know l would have won that race
if you didn't cheat, right?
You hit your head hard.
(LAUGHS)
Don't make me laugh.
(GAVEL BANGING)
All rise.
Please be seated.
Please rise,
Mr. Toretto.
l've listened
to the testimony
and taken into
special consideration
Agent O'Conner's appeal of clemency on
behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly resulted
in the apprehension
of known drug
trafficker Arturo Braga.
However,
this judiciary finds that
one right does not make up for a lifetime
worth of wrongs.
And as such,
l find that l am forced to level the maximum
sentence under California law.
Dominic Toretto,
you are hereby
sentenced to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc maximum security
prison system
without the possibiIity
of earIy paroIe.
This court is adjourned.
(GAVEL BANGS)
(CAR ENGlNES REVVlNG)
(BOTH ARGUlNG lN SPANlSH)